She's not afraid of the big bad wolves.
Little Dead Rotting Hood is a horror film directed by Jared Cohn.
The residents of a small town discover that something more sinister than killer wolves is
lurking in the backwoods: first the wolves start turning up dead...then people.
Sheriff Adam, played by Eric Balfour.
Samantha / Red Rotting Hood, played by Bianca A. Santos.
Deputy Henry, played by Patrick Muldoon.
Officer Victoria, played by Heather Tom.
Officer Scudder, played by Brendan Wayne.
Martha, played by M.J. Brackin.
Little Dead Rotting Hood is a 2016 American horror film written
by Gabriel Campisi and directed by Jared Cohn.
It stars Eric Balfour, Bianca Santos, Romeo Miller,
Patrick Muldoon, Heather Tom and Marina Sirtis.
The film is a mockbuster of the Warner Bros.
romance horror film Red Riding Hood.
The film explores themes of small town, police, wolf,
mythology, little red riding hood.
The tone is dark.